{
    "id": "2d4aa8598ac546b7854ea0877201b294",
    "title": "Sentence Completion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "...................... Dalhousie is the cheapest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Of all hill stations",
                "From all hill stations"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e9c52b68c75e4b98b301c33df760393d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He came to meet me …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in 5 o'clock",
                "on 5 o'clock",
                "at 5 o'clock"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c4f6ed582b374c648d2e3880c6300fd1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very good ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with drawing",
                "in drawing",
                "at drawing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "27b7ebdc155d42bdb947f89d1a3e9920"
        },
        {
            "question": "He shook ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hands with me",
                "my hand"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c72cf04360db4c429fcbcf7c7e12eabb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train was moving .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in full speed",
                "on full speed",
                "at full speed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ca47addd87e74205b802a9e1c8220102"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were accused ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with theft",
                "of theft",
                "about theft"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "377602a6d8d04c19b74329faf447439c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no remedy …..................... .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with this illness",
                "for this illness",
                "to this illness"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "451b9e3ddf344d95be4ba7d92cb04433"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no solution .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of this problem",
                "to this problem",
                "with this problem"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6085bb3fe874f57896f42871de1e883"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in poor health",
                "poor in health",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "80f182fa08fc4443bc37968a5ee01fbb"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must leave .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "within 5 o'clock",
                "before 5 o'clock",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "114406a141dc43ba93484f4aeb5f00d1"
        }
    ]
}